hangintherejack.com 2015-12-07

# X3watch Privacy Policy

**I.   Why does X3watch gather personal information?**  
X3watch gathers personal information in order to provide the award-winning products, service, and support you’ve come to expect from us. As with most transactions, personal information is required in order to set up your account and complete your purchase. But it also helps us provide the product and support information we believe is of greatest interest to you.

 **II.   What information does X3watch collect and how is it used?**  
There are a variety of situations in which X3watch may collect personal information, such as when you register as a customer; purchase one of our products; download free evaluation software, upgrades, or white papers; order email newsletters; respond to a marketing campaign; place orders on our website; or when you’re working with a X3watch service representative. In each of those situations, X3watch only collects the personal information required to meet your needs. Depending on the circumstances, we may ask for your name, company name, Internet domain name, industry, IP address, billing or shipping address, credit card information, email address, fax number, phone number, or other pertinent information.

X3watch uses your information to better understand your needs, provide you with the services you have requested, and with a view to provide you with better service. We may use your information to help you complete a transaction, (including fulfillment of orders and promotional offers), to communicate back to you, to inform you of and update you on services and benefits, and to manage and renew your subscription(s). Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing, maintenance of your subscription, and fraud protection and are not used for other purposes without your permission. Fireproof will keep your personal information for as long as you are a registered subscriber or user of our product(s) and thereafter, for no longer than is reasonably necessary for internal reporting and reconciliation purposes and to provide you with any feedback or information that you might request or require.

 **III.   Does X3watch disclose personal information?**  
No

 **IV.   How does X3watch secure personal information?**  
X3watch uses state-of-the-art security technology to protect our customer data. Access to customer information is restricted to authorized personnel only. Our website is regularly tested for security vulnerabilities to ensure all collected information is secure from unauthorized viewing. Personal customer information is protected in transit via HTTPS and SSL security. Credit card information is transmitted with multiple layers of security, including encryption in storage and SSL in transit. For more information, please review the section on disclosure of information above.

X3watch complies with PCI Data Security Standards that require merchants to implement strong security measures to protect our customers’ credit card information.

 **V.   What privacy policy applies if you follow a link on McAfee’s website?**  
Our site contains links to other websites. If you follow one of those links, you may be leaving X3watch’s website and entering a site not under X3watch control. X3watch does not accept liability for misuse of any information submitted on any site outside its control. We strongly encourage you to read the privacy statements or policies of the linked sites, as their privacy policies may differ from ours.

 **VI.   Does X3watch comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act?**  
Yes. X3watch Privacy Policy complies with all the regulations of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of the United States of America. X3watch does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn we have collected personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that data from our systems.

 **VII.   Contact us**  
If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should first contact the Privacy Program Office of Fireproof. by emailing info@x3watch.com or by calling 626-628-3387.

This privacy policy was last modified on Jan. 28, 2013
